discusstech.org 2013-04-16

# Privacy Policy | Discuss Tech

If you need any more information or have any queries related to our privacy policy, kindly feel free to communicate with us by email at ej.salsan AT gmail.com.

At discusstech.org, the privacy of our users is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document describes the types of personal information is received and collected by discusstech.org and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like any other Web sites, discusstech.org makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

discusstech.org does use cookies to keep the login information.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on discusstech.org send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Discusstech.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve advertisements on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Discusstech.org’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
